Guide to the Vice Provost for Undergraduate Education Records 2001-2015
Vice Provost for Undergraduate Education Records
- Student Services, 2001-07-01-2006-02-02
  - Humanities Seminar, 2001-08-28-2006-02-02
    - Student Services Work Force Planning, 2003-07-30-2003-07-30 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Contents on Cornell University Colleges, the registrar and a number of other departments.
    - Working at EAS, 2003-12-02-2006-04-08 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Emails concerning the Hawaiian EES program
    - Freshman Advising, 2003-10-31-2003-11-04 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Phi Kappa Phi, 2004-11-28-2004-11-28 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - International Teaching Assistant Development Program Center for Learning an Teaching, Cornell University. Program Review 2003-2004, 2003-11-03-2003-11-12 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      Includes a review of the program during the school year of 2003-2004
    - Donlon Apartment, 2004-04-22-2006-02-02 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Cornell University Writer-in-Residence Apartment Usage Proposal Forms
    - Cornell University Field Program in Earth and Environmental Systems, Hawaii Island Spring 2006, 2005-10-03-2005-10-07 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - September 11th, 2001-10-01-2003-04-10
    Files include email, flyers, memos, and program material.
    - The War in Iraq Teach-in and "Speak Out" Free Speech Mic: The War in Iraq, 2003-03-26-2003-04-10 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Teach-In on Israel and Palestine, 2002-04-05-2002-04-10 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - September 11th Speakers, 2001-09-21-2002-02-26 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Cornell University responses to September 11th Tragedies
    - 9/11 Remembrance panels, 2002-07-17-2002-09-06 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Teach-In II, 2001-10-01-2001-10-15 (Box 3, Folder 25)